{
    "id": "0933a33d15314e30b533c656d8284397",
    "title": "For or to",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "25441706881f4433b061a608d124454d",
            "title": "For Or To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We stopped at the pub …………….. a drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He stopped the car ……………… drop her off.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They stopped ………………… get some rest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We use thermometers ……………….. measure temperatures.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was hard ………………… finish on time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to his office ………………… a talk with him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was sent to prison ………………. stealing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was angry with me …………………. lying to her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to Mexico ……………….. meet my brother who lives there.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A barometer is used ………………… measuring pressure.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}